[
    {
        "title": "How Long Ago?"
    },


    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "The Sopranos debuts on HBO / Fatboy Slim’s “Praise You” hits number 1 in the UK / Denver Broncos beat Atlants Falcons in Superbowl XXXIII",
        "answer": "1999"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Great Britain triggered Article 50 which eventually led to Brexit in 2020 / A snap general election is held in the UK, three years before the next is due / Real Madrid beat Juventus 4-1 in the champions league final",
        "answer": "2017"
    },

    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "#MeTOO goes viral / Jamal Kashoggi was murdered in the Saudi Arabian embassy in Istanbul / Prince Harry married Megan Markle",
        "answer": "2018"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "The UK experiences the worst winter since 1946-47 / Summer Holiday featuring Cliff Richard premieres in London / The Beatles release their debut album “Please Please Me”",
        "answer": "1963"
    },

    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "23.5 million tune in to watch “Live and Let Die” on TV. A record TV audience for a film / Robin Cousins wins Gold for GB in the winter Olympics in Lake Placid / Alton Towers opens",
        "answer": "1980"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "The first naturist beach opens near Hastings / Ipswich Town win the FA Cup / The Andrew Lloyd Weber musical Evita opens in London",
        "answer": "1978"
    },

    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "The platinum jubilee of Queen Elizabeth II / Roman Abramovic gives up control of Chelsea FC / Sam Ryder finishes in second place in the Eurovision Song Contest",
        "answer": "2022"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "The Isle of Wight Festival begins featuring Jimi Hendrix, The Who and The Doors / Nijinsky wins The Derby, 2000 Guineas and St Ledger / The Goodies is first broadcast on BBC 2",
        "answer": "1970"
    },

    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Jeremy Clarkson is sacked from his role on Top Gear / Chris Froome wins the Tour de France / England introduces a 5p charge for carrier bags in supermarkets",
        "answer": "2015"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Captain Tom Moore raised £32 million for NHS charities / Argos ended its printed catalogue / We stayed at home a lot",
        "answer": "2020"
    }
]
